Guide to the Darinka Archive 1973-2010 MSS.340
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Audio Recordings, 226302
  - Subseries B: Darinka Music, 226410
    - Motown Gold, undated; ID: 340.0136; 226580 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0136)
      Format: Audiocassette
    - Mr. Lee, undated; ID: 340.0137; 226581 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0137)
    - Murray the K Show, 1963; ID: 340.0138; 226582 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0138)
    - New Order, Promenaders, undated; ID: 340.0139; 226583 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0139)
    - New Sounds, undated; ID: 340.0140; 226584 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0140)
    - OMD - PIL, Wall of Voodoo, undated; ID: 340.0141; 226585 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0141)
    - Party Mix, undated; ID: 340.0142; 226586 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0142)
    - SALSA, undated; ID: 340.0143; 226587 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0143)
    - Police, Patsy Cline, Crazy, undated; ID: 340.0144; 226588 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0144)
    - Elvis Presley, undated; ID: 340.0145; 226589 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0145)
    - Throbbing Gristle, undated; ID: 340.0146; 226590 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0146)
    - The Rage of 1710's, undated; ID: 340.0147; 226591 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0147)
    - Roxy Music, undated; ID: 340.0148; 226592 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0148)
    - Roxy Music, "Flesh and Blood," Bowie, "Ashes to Ashes", undated; ID: 340.0149; 226593 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0149)
    - Sakamoto; James Brown, undated; ID: 340.0150; 226594 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0150)
    - Satie: Parade, undated; ID: 340.0151; 226595 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0151)
    - Thomas Schippers Conducts Samuel Barber, undated; ID: 340.0152; 226596 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0152)
    - Simple Minds, undated; ID: 340.0153; 226597 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0153)
    - Ska, undated; ID: 340.0154; 226598 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0154)
    - Stargazers, undated; ID: 340.0155; 226599 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0155)
    - TOTB - Theory of Total Blame - Las Vegas, undated; ID; 340.0156; 226600 (Box 9, Media ID; 340.0156)
    - Tears, undated; ID: 340.0157; 226601 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0157)
    - Debussy: Prelude al'apres-midi d'un faune, Undated; cuid22001; 226602 (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0158)
    - U.N.C.L.E. - Soundtrack, undated; ID: 340.0159; 226603 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0159)
    - Via Afrika, undated; ID: 340.0160; 226604 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0160)
    - Village Music of Bulgaria, undated; ID: 340.0161; 226605 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0161)
    - Steve Winwood, "Chronicles", undated; ID: 340.0162; 226606 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0162)
    - Yellow Magic Orchestra, undated; ID: 340.0163; 226607 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0163)
    - Yello - Elvis - Devo, undated; ID: 340.0164; 226608 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0164)
    - Yello and Devo, undated; ID: 340.0165; 226609 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0165)
  - Subseries C: Demos and Miscellaneous, 226411
    This subseries contains various demo tapes and unidentified material.
    - The Actuals, undated; ID: 340.0166; 226615 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0166)
    - Alien Planetscapes, "Skylore", undated; ID: 340.0167; 226616 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0167)
    - Green Night Audio Leter, undated; ID: 340.0168; 226617 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0168)
    - Jole Blonde, undated; ID: 340.0169; 226618 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0169)
    - Jenny Bruce, "Demo Tape", undated; ID: 340.0170; 226619 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0170)
    - Bump, undated; ID: 340.0171; 226620 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0171)
    - Doomster, "Refreshes While You Smoke", undated; ID: 340.0172; 226621 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0172)
    - Howard #1, undated; ID: 340.0173; 226622 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0173)
    - Loser's Preshow Song, undated; ID: 340.0174; 226623 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0174)
    - Loser's Preshow Music (Matter of Time), undated; ID: 340.0175; 226624 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0175)
    - Nirvana, "Nevermind", undated; ID: 340.0176; 226625 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0176)
    - Martland Peters 1 & 2, undated; ID: 340.0177; 226626 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0177)
    - David Algeo Smith, "Demo", undated; ID: 340.0178; 226627 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0178)
    - Stephan Smith, "The Ballad of Abner Louima", undated; ID: 340.0179; 226628 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0179)
    - Jeff & Gary 3 Song Demo, undated; ID: 340.0180; 226629 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0180)
    - Tellus: The Audio Cassette Magazine #10, undated; ID: 340.0181; 226630 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0181)
    - Tellus: The Audio Cassette Magazine #20, undated; ID: 340.0182; 226631 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0182)
    - Unfinished Journey, undated; ID: 340.0183; 226632 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0183)
    - Wedding Ceremony, undated; ID: 340.0184; 226633 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0184)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, undated; ID: 340.0185; 226634 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0185)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, undated; ID: 340.0186; 226635 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0186)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, undated; ID: 340.0187; 226636 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0187)
    - Early Recording, undated; ID: 340.0188; 226637 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0188)
    - Don't Do Me Any Favors Pre-Show & House, undated; ID: 340.0189; 226638 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0189)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0190; 226639 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0190)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0191; 226640 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0191)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0192; 226641 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0192)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0193; 226642 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0193)
    - Jousd #5, undated; ID: 340.0194; 226643 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0194)
    - Other Side Jam w/Rob - Guitar; Chuck - Drum, undated; ID: 340.0195; 226644 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0195)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0196; 226645 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0196)
    - Gemini cassette head cleaner, undated; ID: 340.0197; 226646 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0197)
    - Audio cassette head cleaner, undated; ID: 340.0198; 226647 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0198)
  - Subseries D: Additional Sound Recordings, 234638
    Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
    Audiovisual materials in Subseries D are commmercially released material and are available to researchers.
    - After the Fall #12, undated; ID: N/A; 234639 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Original format: Sound Disc: Digital; 4 3/4 in.
    - Below Houston #4, undated; ID: N/A; 234640 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Black and White World #1, undated; ID: N/A; 234641 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Black and White World #3, undated; ID: N/A; 234642 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - RobK ExCorpse, undated; ID: N/A; 234643 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Workdogs In Hell, 1992; ID: N/A; 234644 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Workdogs Old, 1994; ID: N/A; 234645 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Al Jolson: Al Jolson Souvenir Album, 1953; ID: N/A; 234933 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      General
      Contains handwritten annotation: "G Ray keep up the good work [Crocker]"
      Original format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 45rpm
    - Machine & Hummer, "Introvert" 1. "room beyond the door" 2. "angel in rags", undated; ID: N/A; 234934 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Squeegies, 1. "Don't Tread on Flowers" 2. "I Wanna Know Right Now", 1967; ID: N/A; 234935 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Gary, Quazar, 1. "Suicide 2. Lesbian Boy; News, undated; ID: N/A; 234936 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Contains handwritten annotation: "Hey Gary, [Gary] Quazar"
    - Workdogs, 1. "Funny $" 2. "Last Friend's Gone", 1986; ID: N/A; 234937 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Original format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 33 1/3 rpm
    - Finis Coronat Opus (23) - A Jim Sharp Product, 1990; ID: N/A; 234938 (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Contains handwritten annotation: "To Gary - Here's Comin' at Ya --- Jim S -- 12-15-90 1:45 AM Brooklyn"
      Plastikville Records. Side B is blank
      Original format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 46rpm
- Series IV: Video Recordings, 226403
  This series contains video recordings of performances at Darinka.
  - Twad Schuetrum, 1985 November 1; ID: 340.0216; 226677 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0216)
    Original format: VHS
  - Richard Kern, "Manhattan Love Suicides", 1985; ID: 340.0206; 226667 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0206)
  - Kimberly Flynn at Darinka, 1986 September 19; ID: 340.0217; 262990 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0217)
  - Avant Garde Arama with Kimberly Flynn, 1986 October 17; ID: 340.0218; 262991 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0218)
  - Gary Ray: It Comes In Waves (Rough Edit), 1986; 340.0202; 226662 (Box 10, Cassette 340.0202, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 340.0202)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 88 min.
  - The Agaloff Sisters at La Mama (with Kimberly Flynn), 1987 November 14; ID: 340.0219; 262992 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0219)
  - "The Doorman", 1987; ID: 340.0205; 226666 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0205)
  - Jason Brandenburg, "Moonglow", 1987; ID: 340.0208; 226669 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0208)
  - Jason Brandenburg, "Moonglow", 1987; ID: 340.0207; 226668 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0207)
  - Blind Double Date, 1989; ID: 340.0201; 226661 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0201)
  - Theory of Total Blame, Rapp Art Center NYC: Karen Finley, 1989 June 18; ID: 340.0215; 226676 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0215)
  - Church of the Little Green Man at Max Fish, 1990 October; 340.0203; 226663 (Box 10, Cassette 340.0203, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 340.0203)
    Original format: VHS, Duration: 57 min.
  - Czolgosz at PS122, 1990; ID: 340.0204; 226665 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0204)
    Orginal format: VHS
  - Gary Ray: Organic Extensionism, 1992 May 16; ID: 340.0209; 226670 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0209)
  - Biohazardous, 2001; ID: 340.0200; 226660 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0200)
  - Gary Ray hosting AGA, 2003; ID: 340.0199; 226659 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0199)
  - "A Slice of Life," William Kent, undated; ID: 340.0213; 226674 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0213)
  - Chett Grant: A Portrait of the Man, undated; ID: 340.0212; 226673 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0212)
  - "Poison" (Rough Cut), undated; ID: 340.0210; 226671 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0210)
  - "Poltergash", undated; ID: 340.0211; 226672 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0211)
  - Milestone Film, "Spread the Word", undated; ID: 340.0214; 226675 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0214)
- Series V: Data Storage, 226406
  This series contains files and photographs, stored on computer disks.
  - Darinka - Misc. photos - NYC-LES-Performance, 1970's, 1980's, 1990's, Undated; cuid22002; 226691 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0001)
    Format: DVD-R
  - Darinka Bak - ML - World and USA File, Undated; cuid22003; 226692 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0002)
    Format: 5 1/4" DSDD Computer Disk
  - Darinka ML, Undated; cuid22004; 226695 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0003)
  - List, Undated; cuid22005; 226696 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0004)
  - Worldstar disk 6 - Advanced features, Mail list, Undated; cuid22006; 226697 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0005)
  - Copyiipc, Undated; cuid22007; 226699 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0006)
  - SOS Backup Dsk, 2-16-94, 20 pages, circa 1994; cuid22008; 226700 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0007)
  - Play - early SOS, Undated; cuid22009; 226705 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0008)
  - Conn Bak-up - Saved, Undated; cuid22010; 226706 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0009)
  - Data on-file castbox, Undated; cuid22011; 226709 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0010)
- Series VI: Photographs, 267671
  - Photo album (black cover), Undated; cuid22012; 226391 (Box 5)
  - Photo album (red cover), Undated; cuid22013; 226392 (Box 12)
  - Lenticular photograph: Ethyl Eichelberger performing at Darinka, 1986; cuid22014; 267672 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Lenticular photograph: Washington Square Park, circa 1985; cuid22015; 267673 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Lenticular photograph: Larry Steger and Emily Sherman Marynczak at Darinka, circa 1984; cuid22016; 267674 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Series VII. 2015 Accretion, 277553
  - Invitations, 1985-1991; cuid22017; 277554 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Soho, 1991-1992; cuid22018; 277555 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Stop, 1990-1991; cuid22019; 277556 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
- Oversize Series I: Darinka Files, 226303
  This series contains the oversize material separated from series I, including posters and magazine clippings.
  - "Adam Bomb" lyric poster, Undated; cuid22020; 226384 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Carlo McCormick benefit poster, Undated; cuid22021; 226385 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Darinka stencils by Paul Chelstad, Undated; cuid22022; 226386 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - East Village Eye - blurb, 1984 September; cuid22023; 226353 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger / Karen Finley poster, Undated; cuid22024; 226354 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Factory / Market poster, Undated; cuid22025; 226355 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Gigantic - movie poster, Undated; cuid22026; 226356 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Head to the Future poster, Undated; cuid22027; 226357 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Issue of "Backstage", 1985 June 28; cuid22028; 226358 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Johanna Went poster and press release, 1985 June 9; cuid22029; 226359 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mike Osterhout "M" poster, Undated; cuid22030; 226360 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Misc. news articles, 1985, 1987; cuid22031; 226361 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "The New Common Good" article, Undated; cuid22032; 226362 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - New Ice Nights poster, 1986; cuid22033; 226387 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New York Newsday "City Living", 1991 April 4; cuid22034; 226363 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1987-1989; cuid22035; 226364 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Nick Zedd's "School of Shame" poster, Undated; cuid22036; 226365 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Nick Zedd / B. Moran / R. Kern poster, 1984; cuid22037; 226366 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Observe poster, Undated; cuid22038; 226367 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Paper magazine, 1986; cuid22039; 226368 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Soul Samurai poster, 2009; cuid22040; 226369 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Stop Rock Movie poster, undated; cuid22047 (Folder 15)
  - These Showers Can Talk poster, Undated; cuid22041; 226370 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Tubby Boots" poster, Undated; cuid22042; 226371 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Village Voice - "East Side Confidential", 1984 November 13; cuid22043; 226372 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Theory of Total Blame poster, 1988; cuid22044; 226388 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Village Voice - "Kitchen" article, 1985 March 5; cuid22045; 226373 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "When Lithuania Ruled the World part III" poster, Undated; cuid22046; 226374 (Box 3, Folder 22)